samuel.aarga@gmail.com +8613048908553 Shixiacun Futian Shen Zhen Shi, Guang Dong Sheng

### Summary

I am an experienced programmer with over 5 years of experience in web and software development. Excellent reputation for resolving problems and improving customer satisfaction.

I am currently seeking a full-time position that offers professional challenges utilizing interpersonal skills, excellent time management and problem-solving skills.

linkedin:https://www.linkedin.com/in/aarga-sonter

#### **Technologies**

- Docker
- Python(Flask, Django, SQLAlchemy, CMD Scripting, REST)
- Javascript(Reactjs, Vue, Angular, Redux, ES6/ES6)
- HTML5/CSS3/SCSS(sass, bootstrap)
- Typescript
- linux DB
- Jenkins
- · Spring MVC
- PowerShell
- Bash
- · Git Bash
- · Github
- · SQL, MySQL, MongoDB
- · Google cloud
- CICD
- Devops

#### **Experience**

## Web Development Engineer/ Web Tracking Specialyst.

Avature • Shenzhen, Guangdong

01/2019 - 01/2022

Website development, with HTML5, CSS3(Bootstrap,sasss) Type Script, Python JavaScript, ReactJS, Redux, Vue, Angular.

Website restructure with ReactJS/Redux

Performance Testing, Load Testing & Debugging

Constant Creation of React and Vue components.

Oversaw back-end development using Python, SQLAlchemy, Bycrypt to maintain website integrity, security and efficiency.

Built up to date RESTful APIs with Flask.

Conducted administration of the databases.

Employed search engine optimization tactics to increase reach of targeted audience.

Ran debugging tools such as Firebug and Chrome Inspector to eliminate flaws and glitches prior to publishing.

Web scraping using Beautiful Soup and MongoDB

Built and styled new mobile-friendly websites, transitioning legacy presentations to simultaneous easy-to-use versions.

Validated personal coding and third-party code to verify compliance with internal standards and technical requirements.

Collaborated with corporate Director of Operations, regional GM and Shift Leads to pinpoint opportunities for streamlined processes

Collaborated with corporate Director of Operations, regional GM and Shift Leads to pinpoint opportunities for streamlined processes

Play an integral role in customer service and overall sales numbers

Troubleshoot network and production issues and perform root-cause analysis

### Front End Developer

Cube x Inc • Shenzhen, Guangdong 01/2018 - 01/2019

Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML5, JavaScript, Vue ReactJS, AJAX, Ruby and CSS/SCSS(Sass).

Responsive Design & Mobile-First Websites

Built websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS and jQuery.

Drafted customized layout and wireframes based on predetermined parameters and expectations.

Collaborated with graphic design personnel to integrate images as basic site components.

I carried out Search Engine Optimization (SEO) on regular bases

Assisted web presence planning, implementing changes and integrating requested elements to streamline business operations.

Generated web hosting presence to accommodate specified needs, uploading and maintaining files on account.

Provided front-end website development using WordPress, Hubspot and other editing software.

Collaborated with corporate Director of Operations, regional GM and Shift Leads to pinpoint opportunities for streamlined processes

Provided support to over 5 million users in Linux and Mac environment

Revamped UI and app interface for customer-facing e-commerce site with a lot of unique visitors per month

Created front-end prototype for a medical billing web platform that won company's Most Innovative award in 2019

### **Intern Engineer**

BMW Group • Shenyang, Liaoning 05/2017 - 11/2017

Created product design modifications.

Created User Interface Design, User Experience Design. (UI/UX)

Maintained positive work atmosphere by building relationships with co-workers, customers, clients and management.

### **Education**

# **Computer Science & Technology**

Shenyang University Chemical Technology • Shenyang, Liaoning 01/2017

3.4 GPA

### Languages

• English

• Chinese

Skills

- Excellent Communication Skills
- · Problem solving
- Attentive
- · Responsive design
- Multitasking

- Innovative
- Team player
- · Decision Making
- Defect Tracking